Jason Taylor

123 Main Street, Orlando, FL 12345 j.taylor@youremail.com (123) 456-7890

Detail-orientated senior account manager with over seven years of experience in the retail industry. In the past year, I have managed to slash customer complaints by 23% and increased revenue by 36%. Record of working in a fast-paced environment and ensuring premium customer service throughout the sales cycle.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Accounting and Business Management

The University Of Miami, Miami, FL September 2009 - June 2013

Key Skills

- Deal Negotiations
- Risk Evaluation
- Communication
- Organization
- Salesforce Development

Professional Experience

Senior Account Manager

Oceanside Retail, Tampa, FL | September 2016-Present

- Prepare proposals and credit packages for new and existing clients
- Managed 32 high-profile client accounts
- Collaborate with analytics and marketing to determine the main causes of customer complaints and managed to reduce complaints by 57%
- Increased customer retention by 36% across my portfolio
- Establish and maintain relationships with CEOs, CFOs, and finance VPs
- Successfully trained 6 new account managers
- Delivered business presentations to potential and current clients as part of the management team

Account Manager

ABC Retail, Miami, FL | June 2013 - August 2016

- Consistently secure new accounts by cold calling and other innovative methods, which resulted in a 50% increase in annual revenue
- Provided research for new marketing strategies
- Participated in business presentations to new clients
- Delivered premium customer services to encourage customer Loyalty